abovetheinfluence.com 2011-11-02

# Privacy Policy

Through its National Youth Anti-Drug Media Campaign, the White House Office of National Drug Control Policy (ONDCP) created the AbovetheInfluence.com website (the "Site") to help teens become more aware of and assess influences around them, including drugs. We take your privacy very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Your use of this Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy.

**COPPA**  
We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13, to remain consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will make reasonable efforts to delete such information from our records.

**Information You Submit**  
The information we receive depends upon what you do when visiting this site. If you want to send us your comments, you will be asked to enter a nickname or handle.

If you choose to submit a request to the "Contact Us" submission page, we will request your e-mail address only for the purpose of responding. We do not store or share these e-mail addresses and it is not required that an email address be entered here.

If you choose to submit text, photos, video or other materials ("Materials") to the Site, AbovetheInfluence.com will adhere to the following guidelines: 

I. In order to submit Materials, we require the following information: 

  * User Name (which is a nickname, NOT your legal name)  

  * Age

The following registration information is optional:

  * State of Residence
  * E-mail address (so we can notify you if we publish your submission)

Please note, none of the information we require through the registration process is personally identifiable information.

II. To upload (electronically submit) your Materials, you will not have to reveal personally identifiable information.

While your screen name and your state of residence may be collected if you upload Materials to AbovetheInfluence.com, submissions that incorporate any personally identifiable information will be immediately removed from consideration for online posting.

Any company that helps manage this Site has signed an agreement indicating that they will only use the anonymous information collected in aggregate for the purposes for which they were hired.

We reserve the right to disclose any personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable information if we are required to do so by law or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary in order to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process served on us; (c) to protect or defend our legal rights or property, this Site, or its users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of the users of this Site or the general public.

**Information Collected and Stored Automatically**  
In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and the online privacy guidelines of the White House Office of Management and Budget, we do not sell, share or rent any personally identifying information about you.

"Cookies" are small text files from a website that are stored on your hard drive. These small text files make using a website more convenient by saving your passwords and preferences for you. Cookies themselves do not contain any personally identifiable information. We may analyze the information derived from these cookies and match such information with data provided by you or another party.

Abovetheinfluence.com uses 1st party anonymous, persistent cookies. The data from these cookies is collected in aggregate and reported anonymously to the web analytics team to determine how to optimize and improve the Site experience of our visitors. What this means is that in no way is this Site collecting any personally identifiable information from the user without their knowledge and consent. 

While all information gathered is gathered anonymously, if you are still concerned about the potential use of information gathered from your computer by cookies, you can set your browser to prompt you before it accepts a cookie. Most Internet browsers have settings that let you identify and/or reject cookies. These settings are usually located under "Tools" on your browser toolbar. Please note however, that some parts of this Site will not function properly or will be considerably slower if you refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable your cookies settings. The cookies we use automatically collect and store the following information about your visit.

  * The Internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain) and IP address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access the Site;
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access the Site;
  * The date and time you accessed the Site;
  * The pages you visit
  * How long a visit to a page and the Site as a whole lasted
  * If you linked to AbovetheInfluence.com from another website, the address of that website.

**How to Change or Modify Your Permission at Any Time**  
If you wish to remove your online submission from our Site, you may contact us online at http://www.abovetheinfluence.com/contact or write to AbovetheInfluence Coordinator: 100 West 33rd St. 7th floor, New York NY, 10001. Be sure to clearly indicate your screen name, and a brief description of your submission. We will retain your e-mail address and any other information you provide only until we've removed your submission. If we have questions about your correspondence to our "remove submissions" mailbox, we may write back to you for further clarification.

**Internet Security Policy**  
For Site security purposes and to ensure that this Site remains available to all users, this government computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload information or change information on this Site are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 and the National Information Infrastructure Protection Act.

**Links**  
You should be aware that AbovetheInfluence.com links to other websites that are beyond our control. We are not responsible for, nor have we reviewed the content of these sites. These other sites may collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of whose website you're on and read the privacy statements of that website before submitting any personally identifiable information.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

**Contact Information**  
If you have questions about our Privacy Policy or are interested in sending us your suggestions, comments or concerns, please contact us online at http://www.abovetheinfluence.com/contact.

For more information about online privacy, please review the tips provided on the [GetNetWise](http://kids.getnetwise.org/safetyguide/tips/kids.php) website or the   
[Federal Trade Commission's kid's privacy](http://business.ftc.gov/privacy-and-security/children%E2%80%99s-online-privacy) page.

**Security for Your Personal Information**  
We have reasonable and appropriate security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your information.

This Privacy Policy also pertains to the following URLs that are redirected to the AbovetheInfluence.com server: AboveInfluence.com, AbovetheInfluence.org, AbovetheInfluence.net, AbovetheInfluence.tv, Abovetheinfluencemail.com, Freevibe.com, Freevibe.net, Freevibe.org, Freevibemail.com, ImAboveIt.com, ImAbovetheInfluence.com, ThatAintMe.com.

National Youth Anti-Drug Media Campaign  
750 17th Street, NW   
Washington, DC 20503 USA
